JERRY FENG (冯凡)

77 Martin Street (Unit 47), Cambridge, MA 02138

+86-17875468162 • jerryfeng2017@163.com • jfeng@jd17.law.harvard.edu • Wechat: jf45678

SUMMARY

3+ years of equities investing experience in Greater China and USA. Experience involves direct public equities investing (growth, value and special situations) incorporating rigorous modeling, deep research, and strong passion for investing in disruptive business models across TMT, consumer, legal, and education industries. Currently in Beijing, looking to start immediately, but flexible to relocate to other cities in China or Asia.

EDUCATION

Harvard Law School, Cambridge, MA

Graduated May 2017

Juris Doctor (JD) Program

Areas of Focus: Equities and distressed debt investing, corporate & securities law, litigation financing

Yale University, New Haven, CT

Graduated May 2011

B.A. Economics, Phi Beta Kappa, Magna Cum Laude

Cumulative GPA: 3.89/4.00 • Major GPA: 3.95/4.00

WORK EXPERIENCE

ShawSpring Partners LLC, Boston, MA

May 2016 - July 2016

Investment Intern

- Fundamental equities research in China and USA. Covered sectors include: payments, Chinese internet, and US retail.
- Worked with CIO to lead deep-dive research into major Chinese tech holding, helping the fund double-down on its position in June 2016 (up ~90% as of October 2017).
- Helped team formulate deeper and broader equity research strategies.

MIT Investment Management Company (MITIMCo), Cambridge, MA

February 2015 – December 2015

Legal Intern

- Drafted Limited Partnership Agreements (LPA), Offering Memoranda, and side letters for MIT's portfolio of funds.
- Analyzed impact of evolving Chinese Foreign Investment Law on MIT's portfolio holdings (overseas listed Chinese stocks with VIE structures).

Eton Park Capital Management, Hong Kong SAR

August 2012 - May 2014

Investment Professional

- Fundamental equities research in Asia-Pacific markets for the Eton Park Asia Fund (\$1.5 billion AUM), with focus on Greater China/HK.
- Covered consumer products, retail, and TMT. Long and short investments include: short Li & Fung (494 HK), long Midea (000333 CH), long Mead Johnson (MJN US), short Belle (1880 HK), and long Moncler (MONC BIT).
- Developed detailed knowledge of bottoms-up security analysis, industry know-how, emerging markets risk management, and financial modeling.

Ruane, Cunniff & Goldfarb, New York, NY

July 2011 – July 2012

Analyst

- Researched and recommended public equity investments for the Sequoia Mutual Fund.
- Covered U.S. & Canadian retailers, lighting companies, powersports vehicle manufacturers, automotive suppliers, package/parcel shippers, disk-drive manufacturers, and beverage companies.
- Developed extensive financial modeling and risk management skills.

Yale College Student Investment Group, New Haven, CT

May 2009 – May 2010

President

- Largest student organization at Yale dedicated to investing and stock market education.
- Grew portfolio from \$250,000 to \$350,000 from May 2009 to April 2010, based on selection of stocks with strong franchise values and high-quality assets.
- Presented value investing ideas pioneered by Benjamin Graham, Warren Buffett, and Peter Lynch to members.
- Organized trips to investment banks in New York (Goldman Sachs, Credit Suisse, UBS) for networking sessions.

SKILLS & INTERESTS

- Languages: Native Mandarin & English (reading & writing)
- Computer Skills: Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Publisher; STATA: Bloomberg: Capital IO: Sentieo
- *Hobbies*: Investing, Billiards, Travel, Blogging